<metadata xml:lang="en"><Esri><CreaDate>20170504</CreaDate><CreaTime>17575500</CreaTime><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><SyncOnce>TRUE</SyncOnce><ModDate>20170623</ModDate><ModTime>11595000</ModTime><scaleRange><minScale>150000000</minScale><maxScale>5000</maxScale></scaleRange><ArcGISProfile>ItemDescription</ArcGISProfile></Esri><tool name="FloodDataDownloader" displayname="Part - Flood Data Download" toolboxalias="RBI" xmlns=""><arcToolboxHelpPath>c:\arcgis\desktop10.3\Help\gp</arcToolboxHelpPath><parameters><param name="in_poly" displayname="Restoration Site Polygons (Required)" type="Required" direction="Input" datatype="Feature Layer" expression="in_poly"><dialogReference>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The area of the restoration site being assessed. These areas will be compared to the NHDPlus Version 2.1 VPU to determine which catchments the sites intersect with.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</dialogReference></param><param name="VUB" displayname="NHD Plus Vector Processing Unit" type="Optional" direction="Input" datatype="Feature Layer" expression="{VUB}"><dialogReference>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Vector Processing Unit boundary polygons defining the NHDPlus Vector Processing Units for each region where data is available. If no dataset is specified the tool will by default use the VUB "BoundaryUnit.shp" downloaded to the NHDPlusV21 folder in the same directory as the tool. If no dataset is specified and the default dataset is not in the expected location this tool will fail to run.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</dialogReference></param><param name="outTable" displayname="Download Folder" type="Optional" direction="Output" datatype="Feature Class" expression="{outTable}"><dialogReference>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;A file name and location must be specified for the dataset that results from the analysis. In this case that is the NHDPlus Catchment files that are downloaded. For the Full Indicator Assessment tool to perform Flood Risk Reduction Benefit analysis this file must be saved in the default File Geodatabase "NHDPlus_Downloads.gdb" within the NHDPlusV21 folder downloaded to the same directory as the tool. For example ~\Rapid-Benefit-Indicators-Tools\py_Spatial\NHDPlusV21\NHDPlus_Downloads.gdb&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;If you wish to save Catchment files in an alternative location, the Partial tool Flood Risk Reduction must be used for Flood Risk Reduction Benefit analysis instead of the Full Indicator Assessment tool.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</dialogReference></param></parameters><summary>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Flood Data Download tool determined what catchments are needed for delineating upstream and downstream areas for each site and then downloads the catchments for that region.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</summary><usage>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Download NHDPlus V2.1 catchments for use when calculating Flood Risk Reduction Benefits.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</usage></tool><dataIdInfo><idCitation><resTitle>Part - Flood Data Download</resTitle></idCitation><idCredit>Justin Bousquin</idCredit><searchKeys><keyword>Flood Risk Reduction Benefits; NHD+; Data Download; RBI; Rapid Benefit Indicators; Ecosystem Services</keyword></searchKeys><resConst><Consts><useLimit>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The United States Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) RBI project code is provided on an "as is" basis and the user assumes responsibility for its use. EPA has relinquished control of the information and no longer has responsibility to protect the integrity, confidentiality, or availability of the information. Any reference to specific commercial products, processes, or services by service mark, trademark, manufacturer, or otherwise, does not constitute or imply their endorsement, recomendation or favoring by EPA. The EPA seal and logo shall not be used in any manner to imply endorsement of any commercial product or activity by EPA or the United States Government.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</useLimit></Consts></resConst><idAbs>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Flood Data Download tool determined what catchments are needed for delineating upstream and downstream areas for each site and then downloads the catchments for that region.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</idAbs></dataIdInfo><distInfo><distributor><distorFormat><formatName>ArcToolbox Tool</formatName></distorFormat></distributor></distInfo><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="005"/></mdHrLv></metadata>
